export const data = [
    {
        question: "Who was trying to make Harry Potter fall from his broom during Quiditch Match in Chambers of Secret?",
        option1: "Prof. Dumbledore",
        option2: "Draco Malfoy",
        option3: "Prof. Quirrel",
        option4: "Prof. Snape",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Who removes all the bones from Harryâ€™s arm?",
        option1: "Gilderoy Lockhart",
        option2: "Hagrid",
        option3: "Voldemort",
        option4: "Neville Longbottom",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "How many Horcruxes did Voldemort create intentionally?",
        option1: 5,
        option2: 6,
        option3: 7,
        option4: 'none',
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "In Book 4, which two teams compete for the Quidditch World Cup?",
        option1: "Bulgaria and Ireland",
        option2: "China and India",
        option3: "England and France",
        option4: "Japan and Germany",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the actual heir of slytherin in Chambers of Secret?",
        option1: "Draco Malfoy",
        option2: "Severus Snape",
        option3: "Harry Potter",
        option4: "Tom Riddle",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Which character had the code name 'Moony'?",
        option1: "Remus Lupin",
        option2: "Peter Pettigrew",
        option3: "Serius Black",
        option4: "James Potter",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "How does one ward off a Dementor?",
        option1: "Patronus Charm",
        option2: "Riddikulus Charm",
        option3: "Lumos Charm",
        option4: "Expelliarmus Spell",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "In Book 5, Snape is assigned to teach Harry what type of magic? ",
        option1: "Legilimency",
        option2: "Dark Arts Defence",
        option3: "Advanced Potion Making",
        option4: "Occlumency",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "When is Harry's birthday?", 
        option1: "July 31 1980",
        option2: "July 30 1980",
        option3: "June 10 1975",
        option4: "May 30 1980",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What spell does Harry discover written in the Half-Blood Prince's potions textbook in Book 6, and who invented it?", 
        option1: "Sectumsempra, Severus Snape",
        option2: "Levicorpus, Gellert Grindelwald",
        option3: "Expelliarmus, Albus Dumbledore",
        option4: "Crucio, Bellatrix Lestrange",
        ans: 1,
    }

];